bestdenki.com.sg 2013-05-30

# Privacy Policy | BEST Denki Singapore

BEST Denki  (Singapore) Pte Ltd and its affiliates (collectively, The Company) believes in your personal information privacy that you provide in the course of using our Website. It is important for us to explain what information is collected and how it is used and what you can do to opt out if you so choose.

**General**

This Privacy Policy applies to all identifiable personal information collected from the Company’s Website from consumers using our Website.

**Personal Information**

We collect your personal information to

  * Better develop the The Company’s online and offline experience for you. We will use the information to improve our products mix, improve our customer services and make our website more attractive and informative to you.
  * In the course of interacting with you we may collect information on the website registration and a cookie is used in your computer to store your web browsing settings for your web browsing convenience.
  * Fulfill eCommerce transactions
  * Send out The Company’s newsletter subscriptions, alerts and other information that would be of interest to you
  * Take part in The Company’s Online community areas
  * When you apply for a job with our company.
  * When you apply for a The Company’s Credit Card(s)

**Where is it collected?**

You have the choice of entering your personal information when you register at our website(s), subscribing to newsletters, registering in promotions, competitions or when you register your product(s) bought at The Company’s store outlets or Online eCommerce area.

**It’s your choice**

You can choose to tell us not to use your personal information for marketing activities by emailing [stop@bestdenki.com.sg](mailto:stop@bestdenki.com.sg) or modifying your personal information in our website under your registered user account.

**What will we do with your information?**

We will use your information to better understand your needs. We may provide you with marketing surveys pertaining to your interests and hobbies and purchasing preferences, feedback forms to improve our website user experience, for marketing activities like sending out newsletters (if you choose to accept it), and for fulfilling any eCommerce activity you, our customer, may be engaged in.

**When will we share your information?**

The Company will not sell your personal information to a third party. The Company will only share your information with third parties if:

  * The Company is doing a promotional activity with a third party. In this circumstance, you will be informed of such a relationship. The third party will have their own privacy policy which may differ from The Company’s Privacy Policy, and is out of the control of The Company.
  * To fulfill your purchase transaction, a third party (such as a delivery company) may be involved and require your information. The Company requires these third party companies to keep your information confidential and not to use it for any other purpose other than to fulfill an order.
  * It is required by Law to prevent, or to combat, fraud.

**Contact us**

You can contact us [here](http://go.bestdenki.com.sg/content/contact-us)
